CHEONGSAN CHICKEN
THIS IS A SAFE ZONE
THIS IS A RESTRICTED AREA
RESCUE TEAM 1 NAM SO-JU
I LOVE YOU, YOON HYEONG-GEUN
I'LL SAVE YOU
HOW MUCH TIME MUST PASS FOR THIS TO END?
I MISS YOU, PLEASE JUST SHOW UP
I HOPE YOU'RE OKAY UP THERE
I MISS YOU, PARK JU-YEONG
I LOVE YOU, U-GI
FLOWING WATER ENVELOPS ME
AND FLOWS INTO MY PAINFUL MEMORIES
I'LL LET YOU GO NOW
NATIONAL ASSEMBLY HEARING ON
BOMBING OF HYOSAN POSTPONED INDEFINITELY
HEARING POSTPONED UNTIL
SITUATION IS RESOLVED, MARTIAL LAW LIFTED
I-SAK, I MISS YOU
NAM-RA, COME BACK
CHEONG-SAN, I LOVE YOU
LEE CHEONG-SAN
ZOMBIE VICTIM SPECIAL ADMISSION
HIGH SCHOOL SENIORS
WHO SUFFERED THE ZOMBIE ATTACK
MUST BE GIVEN
SPECIAL ADMISSIONS INTO COLLEGES
KOREAN RED CROSS
EMERGENCY RELIEF SUPPLIES
I MISS YOU ALL
THIS IS A SAFE ZONE
HYOSAN HIGH SCHOOL
ALL CHARACTERS, LOCATIONS, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND EVENTS IN THIS SHOW ARE FICTIONAL.
Subtitle translation by: Jeong Lee